<question>
        <q id="1">
            What is the basic unit of electric charge? <blank id="1"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="2">
            What is the SI unit of electric current? <blank id="2"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="3">
            Define electric current. <blank id="3"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="4">
            What is the difference between a conductor and an insulator?  <blank id="4"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="5">
            Explain the concept of voltage. <blank id="5"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="6">
            State Ohm's law. <blank id="6"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="7">
            What is resistance and what is its unit? <blank id="7"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="8">
            Draw a simple circuit diagram with a battery, a resistor, and a switch. <blank id="8"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="9">
            What is the difference between a series circuit and a parallel circuit? <blank id="9"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="10">
            In a series circuit, how is the total resistance calculated? <blank id="10"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="11">
            In a series circuit, the current is the <blank id="11">_____</blank> through each component.
        </q>
        <q id="12">
            In a series circuit, the total voltage is equal to the <blank id="12">_____</blank> of the individual voltages across each component.
        </q>
        <q id="13">
            If two resistors of 5 ohms and 10 ohms are connected in series, what is the total resistance? <blank id="13"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="14">
            In a parallel circuit, how is the total resistance calculated? <blank id="14"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="15">
            In a parallel circuit, the voltage across each branch is <blank id="15">_____</blank>.
        </q>
        <q id="16">
            In a parallel circuit, the total current is the <blank id="16">_____</blank> of the currents in each branch.
        </q>
        <q id="17">
            If two resistors of 5 ohms and 10 ohms are connected in parallel, what is the total resistance? <blank id="17"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="18">
            Why are appliances in a house connected in parallel and not in series? <blank id="18"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="19">
            What is a short circuit and why is it dangerous? <blank id="19"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="20">
            What is the function of a fuse or a circuit breaker?  <blank id="20"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="21">
            Explain how electricity is generated in a power plant.  <blank id="21"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="22">
             What are some examples of renewable energy sources used to generate electricity? <blank id="22"></blank>
        </q>
         <q id="23">
            Draw a circuit diagram with three resistors in series, connected to a battery.  Label the resistors R1, R2, and R3, each with different resistance values. Calculate the total resistance and the current flowing through the circuit if the battery voltage is 12V. <blank id="23"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="24">
             Draw a circuit diagram with two resistors in parallel connected to a battery. Calculate the total resistance and the current through each resistor and the total current supplied by the battery if the voltage is 6V and the resistances are 2Ω and 3Ω respectively.  <blank id="24"></blank>
        </q>

</question>