<question>
        <q id="1">
            Combine the following sentences using a relative clause: The dog barked at the mailman. The dog was a German Shepherd. <blank id="1"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="2">
            Combine the following sentences using a relative clause: I visited the museum. The museum had an exhibit on dinosaurs.<blank id="2"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="3">
            Combine the following sentences using a relative clause: The student failed the test. The student didn't study.<blank id="3"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="4">
            Combine the following sentences using a relative clause:  The car broke down. The car was old.<blank id="4"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="5">
            Combine the following sentences using a relative clause: The book is interesting. I borrowed the book from the library.<blank id="5"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="6">
           Identify the relative pronoun and its antecedent: The movie that we watched last night was very suspenseful. Relative Pronoun: <blank id="6"></blank> Antecedent: <blank id="7"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="7">
           Identify the relative pronoun and its antecedent:  The woman who lives next door is a doctor. Relative Pronoun: <blank id="8"></blank> Antecedent: <blank id="9"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="8">
            Identify the relative pronoun and its antecedent: The restaurant where we ate dinner was expensive. Relative Pronoun: <blank id="10"></blank> Antecedent: <blank id="11"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="9">
            Fill in the appropriate relative pronoun: The city <blank id="12">_____</blank> I grew up has changed a lot.
        </q>
        <q id="10">
            Fill in the appropriate relative pronoun: The person <blank id="13">_____</blank> called you left a message.
        </q>
        <q id="11">
            Fill in the appropriate relative pronoun: This is the house <blank id="14">_____</blank> Jack built.
        </q>
        <q id="12">
             Fill in the appropriate relative pronoun:  The reason <blank id="15">_____</blank> I'm late is because of traffic.
        </q>
        <q id="13">
           Explain the difference in meaning between "restrictive" and "non-restrictive" relative clauses.  <blank id="16"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="14">
           Write an example of a sentence with a restrictive relative clause: <blank id="17"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="15">
           Write an example of a sentence with a non-restrictive relative clause: <blank id="18"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="16">
           Correct the error in the following sentence: The man which I met yesterday was very kind.<blank id="19"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="17">
            Correct the error in the following sentence (If any): The house, which is located on a hill, has a beautiful view.<blank id="20"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="18">
            Correct the error in the following sentence:  My friend, who he is a doctor, works at the local hospital.<blank id="21"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="19">
           Is the relative clause in the following sentence restrictive or non-restrictive?  The students who studied hard passed the exam. <blank id="22"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="20">
            Is the relative clause in the following sentence restrictive or non-restrictive? My sister, who lives in London, is visiting next month. <blank id="23"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="21">
            Rewrite the following sentence using a reduced relative clause: The cake which was baked by my mother was delicious.<blank id="24"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="22">
            Rewrite the following sentence using a reduced relative clause: The emails that were sent by the CEO were important. <blank id="25"></blank>
        </q>
        <q id="23">
             Rewrite the following sentence using a relative clause: He is the author. His books are famous. <blank id="26"></blank>
        </q>
         <q id="24">
             Rewrite the following sentence using a relative clause: This is the city. I was born there. <blank id="27"></blank>
        </q>

</question>